HAKAN KARADENIZ



Personal

Phone number

+90 531 392 1672 / +351 915 779 510

Email

hakan.karadeniz@outlook.com

Gender Male

Driving licence

R

Website hakankaradeniz.github.io

LinkedIn
linkedin.com/in/karadenizhakan

Interests

- Playing Piano
- Travelling
- Playing Football

Languages

Turkish

English • • •

I completed my 4 years education year at the Department of Electrical and Electronics Engineering at Istanbul Bilgi University. I want to implement and manage national and international projects that touch people's lives in a company where I can use my experience, demonstrate my technical knowledge and skills, and be useful. In line with this goal, I continue to improve myself with the principle of life long learning.

Education and Qualifications

Electrical and Electronics Engineering

Oct 2017 - 2022

Istanbul Bilgi University, Istanbul

Business / Faculty of Open and Distance Education

Oct 2020 - Present

Istanbul University

Work experience

Electrical and Computer Engineering Department Intern Sep 2022 - May 2023 University of Coimbra, Coimbra, Portugal

- Using the EAGLE program
- PCB design

Software Development Intern

Apr 2022 - Jul 2022

Nettsi Informatics Technology, Istanbul, Turkey

- -Using command screen with Linux and mostly used commands.
- -Object Orianted Programming with C++, Standart Template Library, VSCode extensions.
- -I observed very clearly how important it is to work as a team and why the SCRUM is so important.
- -Basic knowledge about TCP/UDP protocols, OSI Layers, WireShark.
- -Using Git commands

Working Student in University

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

Istanbul Bilgi University, Istanbul/Eyüpsultan

- Introducing the University to people who come as guests
- Business management and sharing
- Presenting in front of the community
- Team work

Electrical & Electronics Engineer Intern

Sep 2020 - Oct 2020

YAMAS A.Ş., Bursa/Nlüfer

- Learning the production process
- Managing the operation
- Detailed information on occupational health and safety
- Learning to use the IFS program
- Basic knowledge about Maintenance
- Team work

Skills

Microsoft Office Tools

Team Player Problem Solving

Result Oriented

GitHub

github.com/hakankaradeniz